An AI agent

Usage: goosed.exe [COMMAND]

Commands:
  configure     Configure goose settings
  info          Display goose information
  mcp           Run one of the mcp servers bundled with goose
  acp           Run goose as an ACP agent server on stdio
  session       Start or resume interactive chat sessions [aliases: s]
  project       Open the last project directory [aliases: p]
  projects      List recent project directories [aliases: ps]
  run           Execute commands from an instruction file or stdin
  recipe        Recipe utilities for validation and deeplinking
  schedule      Manage scheduled jobs [aliases: sched]
  gateway       Manage gateways for external platform integrations [aliases: gw]
  update        Update the goose CLI version
  term          Terminal-integrated goose session
  local-models  Manage local inference models [aliases: lm]
  completion    Generate the autocompletion script for the specified shell
  help          Print this message or the help of the given subcommand(s)

Options:
  -h, --help     Print help
  -V, --version  Print version
